<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-09-16T18:09:19+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Cyberpunk 2077</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Cyberpunk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cyberpunk 2077" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Cyberpunk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Cyberpunk.html">&lt;!-- Cyberpunk.md --&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;cyberpunk-2077-is-an-upcoming-role-playing-video-game-developed-and-published-by-cd-projekt&quot;&gt;Cyberpunk 2077 is an upcoming role-playing video game developed and published by CD Projekt&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cyberpunk 2077 is being developed by CD Projekt Red, an internal studio within CD Projekt, using the REDengine 4 game engine. They launched a new division in Wrocław and partnered with Digital Scapes to assist production. Around 450 total staff members are involved with the development, exceeding the number that worked on the studio’s previous game, The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt. Cyberpunk 2020 creator Mike Pondsmith consulted on the project, and actor Keanu Reeves has a starring role.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html">Cyberpunk 2077 is an upcoming role-playing video game developed and published by CD Projekt</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%5Cassets%5Cimg%5Cgithub.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Witcher.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Witcher</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/Witcher.html">&lt;!-- Witcher.md --&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-witcher-3-wild-hunt-is-a-2015-action-role-playing-game-developed-and-published-by-cd-projekt&quot;&gt;The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt is a 2015 action role-playing game developed and published by CD Projekt.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and is based on The Witcher series of fantasy novels by Andrzej Sapkowski. It is the sequel to the 2011 game The Witcher 2: Assassins of Kings. Played in an open world with a third-person perspective, players control protagonist Geralt of Rivia, a monster hunter known as a witcher, who is looking for his missing adopted daughter on the run from the Wild Hunt: an otherworldly force determined to capture and use her powers. Players battle the game’s many dangers with weapons and magic, interact with non-player characters, and complete main-story and side quests to acquire experience points and gold, which are used to increase Geralt’s abilities and purchase equipment. Its central story has several endings, determined by the player’s choices at certain points in the game.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jill</name></author><summary type="html">The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt is a 2015 action role-playing game developed and published by CD Projekt.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%5Cassets%5Cimg%5Cgithub.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">World of Warcraft</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/WorldofWarcraft.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="World of Warcraft" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/WorldofWarcraft</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/20/WorldofWarcraft.html">&lt;!-- Worldofwarcraft.md --&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;world-of-warcraft-wow-is-a-massively-multiplayer-online-role-playing-game-mmorpg-released-in-2004-by-blizzard-entertainment&quot;&gt;World of Warcraft (WoW) is a massively multiplayer online role-playing game (MMORPG) released in 2004 by Blizzard Entertainment.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and is the fourth released game set in the Warcraft fantasy universe. World of Warcraft takes place within the Warcraft world of Azeroth, approximately four years after the events at the conclusion of Blizzard’s previous Warcraft release, Warcraft III: The Frozen Throne. The game was announced in 2001, and was released for the 10th anniversary of the Warcraft franchise on November 23, 2004. Since launch, World of Warcraft has had seven major expansion packs released for it: The Burning Crusade, Wrath of the Lich King, Cataclysm, Mists of Pandaria, Warlords of Draenor, Legion, and Battle for Azeroth.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ted</name></author><summary type="html">World of Warcraft (WoW) is a massively multiplayer online role-playing game (MMORPG) released in 2004 by Blizzard Entertainment.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%5Cassets%5Cimg%5Cwow.png" /></entry></feed>